Developed by ℍ𝕠𝕥 𝔸𝕧𝕚𝕒𝕟#3721

Used in discord.gg/n6NyeQB

Questions/Bug reports can be sent to me

Early phase of the bot, requires patience. This bot will NOT be running 24/7 for quite some time, don't rely on it.

Advertisement:

	Interested in Garry's Mod? Maybe not your cup of tea, how about Rust? Well join our discord where we run active servers for both, and more!
We use a great bot that has lots of special features for ONLY this server!